[Music]
i'm sorry
fantastic two days
celebrating 10 years of the comedy
factory
it's been a long journey and it's
[Music]
comedy can take you to unimaginable
places that's a jail
[Music]
foreign
it was not even
[Music]
foreign
cut out
ever right free subscription of this
master class if you subscribe to this
channel so click yes subscribe
but how do you learn comedy
comedy
is
[Music]
hello
i
[Music]
so it was just comedians in car getting
some
shimoli
[Laughter]
faces splattered with feces yeah
yeah i know
[Laughter]
so we were having shimoli at a roadside
shawarma place what is a shimoni that is
a good question well it's a finely diced
orange chicken roasted until it's
crunchy yet soft marinated with
mayonnaise and lettuce strings served in
a sweet hot dog pie
so we have been producing live comedy
shows in gujarat since a decade now and
our team had not met other comedians
since a long time so it was a great
reunion of sorts by the way so
[Music]
done
uh
i do in gujarat with 50 occupancy took
care of the sanitization we took care of
the social distancing and all the
government norms it was just so
heartwarming to see each other after a
very long time
and of course you are excited to be back
in the green room
so it's gonna
what are you excited
[Music]
[Applause]
right
[Music]
[Applause]
comedy factory and of course 10 years 10
times
meanwhile back in the lowlands
[Music]
okay
[Laughter]
all right super excited 2019 my last
update is this beautiful venue if you
can turn around and show it to one shot
if you don't want to that you can take a
fat shot but yeah this is the best room
in gujarat
but you know what we actually do before
going on stage
[Music]
[Applause]
12 seconds later
much later
[Applause]
[Music]
a few inches later
[Applause]
five minutes later
[Music]
well comedy is not easy and coming to
the main question how do you learn
comedy well it's by facing the audience
and being on stage and it can be
anywhere anytime as they say experience
is the best teacher thank you so very
much to everybody who supported us in
this 10 years journey of being a team of
being a collective and everybody who has
been part of these shows are part of our
family
[Music]
oh
[Applause]
[Music]
you